Thank you for watching!
mmm
Hmmm...
Is the source that started it a sneeze?
Sneeze.
Good evening, ladies and gentlemen.
Good evening.
I wonder if this is connected, if everyone can see it.
It's a little bit easy.
I'll just say that I'm here.
It started with Mire-chan's sneeze.
We're Shrimp Shichugaku.
We are Ebi Shichugaku!
So this time, we'll be doing the showroom remotely.
I'll be doing it remotely.
What do you mean by "remote delivery"?
It's something I remember from a very long time ago.
I remember when we did it for the Corona Disaster.
But you did it remotely last time too?
That's right.
Yeah, how many times?
Did you do it yourself this time?
Yes, I did.
Cocona participated?
I participated.
Me, Cocona and Nono?
I see. What was it like for you guys?
I flew away for a moment... somewhere.
I froze for a moment.
That's what a remote does, right?
It's a common occurrence.
Freeze for a moment
So, that's how it is now.
I'm sure there will be some interruptions in the delivery, but I hope everyone will be patient and enjoy the show with me.
I'm Yasumoto, and I'm going to be your host this time, too.
I'm glad to hear you're doing well.
Yes, I'm glad to see that you're all well, and to those of you who couldn't make it to Idol Square, it's been a long time since I've seen you talking like this.
I feel better!
Thank you very much.
And here are today's members!
Yes, the number in attendance is Mire from Lucky's Bone. Pleased to meet you.
Hi, good to meet you.
Yes, attendance number 13, I'm Sakurai Kokono. Pleased to meet you.
I'm looking forward to working with you.
Well, I'd like to get started right away.
Are you with me for the title call?
Like normal.
We have a policy that one of us can show up.
You have a policy? Okay, let's go.
I'll go.
The Shrimp Club.
The showroom of the admission association.
Showroom?
Yay
Yay!
He says he won't say anything about Mr. Hoshina.
Thank you.
Shall we go there?
I'm sorry.
So today is the 44th edition of the Shrimp Shack's funny and hilarious showroom.
The 44th?
Forty-four times?
I thought I was doing more.
So...
Kiichi, you mean you've done 44 showrooms?
What?
But that's great.
That's great. You've been doing it for a long time.
Yes, so this delightful and funny showroom of the shrimpers
Our
It's like a sister showroom of Ukka's showroom.
So, let's introduce the ranking of the showrooms.
Okay, I'll go this way.
Okay, here we go.
First of all, 5th place
Thank you very much.
Okay, fourth place goes to...
Let's see...
Thank you, Ms. Kosanka Koyama.
Please, of course.
In third place, 553. Thank you.
Thank you very much.
Second place goes to Tamayori.
And first place goes to Tsuna-san
Thank you very much.
Yes, Anonymous et Croissant
I guess I'll just book my sister's trip to äm.
Also ilto дости on
Free awaits you!
I'd like to invite you to register for the showroom and give a free gift.
You can get it for free or for a fee.
You can get it.
Yes, sir.
How are you doing today?
How many are here today?
You know, just now... just now...Hey, you know, just now... just now...
There was a shot of Tokyo Dome, and they were running around.
Tokyo Dome?
Is someone there?
Someone I saw on the screen...
There's someone else at Tokyo Dome.
Is this a surprise?
Surprise?
Is it a surprise?
What's Tokyo? I'm curious.
A day and a half, right? I don't know.
It's not in the sun, that's for sure.
I'm sure he'd love to go to the beach, but he can't.
I'm sure he'd love to go.
You done? Now.
I haven't heard. I haven't heard.
Everyone seems to be getting excited by the comments.
And if you click on the Twitter icon at the bottom of the screen.
If you click on the Twitter icon at the bottom of the screen, you can advertise this broadcast on Twitter.
Let's do it remotely.
So, the manager got you a job and you went?
Okay. Okay, let's see...
What's a good pose?
What do you like?
After all, we're all three Ebichu gals here...
Oh! Gyaru?
So we're all three gals here!
That's why we're called gal pies.
Aya, are you a gal?
She's a gal, right?
Yes, I am.
Like this?
Galpy with both hands.
Two hands, gal pi.
Then, please.
Please do.
It's so shiny!
That's so white, Mire-chan!
Hey.
What's up?
Did I get it?
Not yet.
What's so white?
Mmm-hmm.
Oh, wait.
You never know when they'll take it.
He said okay.
Thank you.
I don't know.
I don't remember at all.
Somehow, somehow, someway.
So here it is.
I'm going to make an announcement on our official website, too.
We'll announce it on our official page, too.
So please tweet about it
I'd appreciate it if you could tweet it and promote it.
So, you know...
Our recent
We've been...
We've been working on a project called
We participated in an idol festival called "Idol Square" during that time.
We performed at an idol festival called Idol Square.
Unfortunately, there were only 6 of us.
It's been a long time since we've been to an idol festival like this.
It's always a good time, isn't it?
It was fun.
It was fun, wasn't it?
It's kind of nice, isn't it?
That exquisite...
I know you love that atmosphere.
There are people who support EBITCHU, right? There are people who support us now, right?
And there are also fans who like various idols and have left EBITCHU, but can be reunited with them...
I think it's really fun to have that kind of mix.
Also, it's a common thing for me to see idols that I don't know much about Ebiichu, who are from totally different genres, come out at these events.
I'm not sure if it's because I don't know them well or if it's because I don't know them at all, but I'm sure it's because I don't know them at all.
And they make the people with pockets of faces smile at the end of the show.
It's like they want to make this person smile for sure.
Like, "I want her to smile now.
That's right.
That's true.
Yes, I really enjoy that feeling.
I felt like we all became one.
I could tell by the expressions on everyone's faces.
So in that sense, it was fun because I felt like it's been a while since I've had that feeling.
That's true.
For me, it was the first time since I joined this production
It was my first time at a festival like this.
It was my first time at a festival like this since I joined this production, and it was almost the first time for me, so I had a lot of pressure and nervousness about dancing with the older members.
But when I got on stage, I really enjoyed the atmosphere and the fans were smiling at me.
The fans were smiling at me, and the older lady members were smiling at me, too.
Are you okay? I was really saved by the fact that they looked at me like I was their coconut.
Oh, but I was so nervous, wasn't I?
I was so nervous.
It must have been a lot of pressure.
Yeah, I guess so.
Even backstage.
We're very at-home, so the sisters are pretty relaxed.We're very at-home, so the sisters' team was pretty relaxed.
I watched the other teams on the monitor and relaxed.
But Cocona was the only one who danced in front of the mirror... and made decisions for herself.
I thought she was in the Super Olympics.
She was doing it so well.
You know...
But you know what? I don't feel uncomfortable at all.
I might have been a little nervous about being alone, but I felt totally comfortable.
It's been a while since I've seen that many people.
That's right. It feels a little small, doesn't it?
I know.
I'm so used to it that I thought there weren't enough recordings.
I felt a little bit sad again.
But you know, next week or this Friday in Niigata.
LUNCH DAY!
We'll be back in Niigata for the first day of the tour.
We'll finally be able to show you the tour that we've prepared with all 9 of us.
I'll be able to show you the tour that we've prepared, but I'll be nervous when I don't have any time to spare.
That's true.
Last week, we were really packed.
I was like, "Let's do it.
But now that I've had a break...
I'm going to start from scratch again.
You know?
New songs.
Are we going to perform them or not?
I'm sure they will.
It's cool.
I don't know.
It would be bad if they didn't play any songs.
That's for sure.
You know, you're in earbuds, and you say you can sing your heart out for two songs.
That's true.
I'm looking forward to it.
What do you think?
Why are you sitting at the end? You're making a "why are you sitting at the end?" sound.
What?
Why are you sitting at the end? I said, "Why are you sitting on the edge?
The end?
Oh, he said the end.
This way. Maybe just a little bit further.
Oh, it's okay.
He was sitting at the end of the sofa.
Sumin was sitting there.
What are you two doing here?
I'm sorry, I stopped you.
No, not at all.
Hey, do you have any enthusiasm for the tour?
Do you have any enthusiasm for the tour?
COCONUT is...
It's your first time on the COCONUT tour, right?
Yes, it is.
I often perform in Tokyo.
So this is the first time I'm going to tour in the provinces.
I think there will be a lot of people who see us here for the first time.
So at that time
I want to see more and more performances.
I want to do my best to give such a wonderful performance.
I want to feel the atmosphere of each region.
Yes, I want to feel the atmosphere of each region.
I can't put it into words yet, but I'm sure I'll be able to feel the atmosphere of each region.
I can't put it into words yet, but
I can't put it into words yet, but it's really different.
I see.
It's a characteristic of each region.
What do you think? Mire-chan?
Yes, I think so.
But there are many places we haven't been to in a long time.
For a long time it was normal for Ebichu to have a tour every year.
But for the past two years, we haven't been able to tour so much.
We did have the Move tour, but it wasn't with the full band.
It's been a long time since we had a proper series of Ebichu tours, so we had to stop with the memories of Ninja at that time.
I think there are a lot of people who still have the memories of the ninjas from that time.
I hope I can show the goodness of Ebiichu as we continue to update our memories.
But I've been wanting to see you for a long time, but I couldn't go to see you.
I've heard a lot of people say that.
That's right.
It's been frustrating and we've both been a little worried about it.
So I'm really happy that we can finally meet.
I'm so glad to finally meet you.
It's the first time I know of him.
There are a lot of people who have come to like Ebichu in this Corona disaster.
I want to show them a live Ebichu.
That's right.
I'm really looking forward to seeing you guys in real life.
I'm really looking forward to it... because I think that seeing Ebichu in real life is a little bit different from seeing it on the screen.
I think it's very different to see EBITCHU on screen than to see EBITCHU in real life.
I think you can really feel the passion or the personal side of EBITCHU when it is live.
I hope that those of you who are coming for the first time can look forward to it with anticipation.
I hope you will come and enjoy the show for the first time. I hope everyone will come to the show.
I'm looking forward to it.
I'll be waiting for you. So, that's it,
I would like to go to today's project.
Yes.
A funny and fugly mute game.
Yay.
Mute.
So, we're going to go remote.So, I've been working remotely.
The scary thing is that the voice that is speaking
mute, where you can't hear what's being said.
Yes, there is.
If you can use the mute in an interesting way
If you can use mute in an interesting way, there is nothing to be afraid of anymore.
So, I would like to compete with my sister to see who can use the mute the best.
Yes, you can do anything you want, like disappear from the screen, use props, and so on.
I see.
The act of continuing to stream without noticing that you're muted.
The act of continuing to deliver without realizing you're muted.
It was a muted version of freeze game, wasn't it?
Yes, it's a mute version of the freeze game we played last time.
So, what shall we do first?
Who do you want to go first?
Uh-huh.
I'll let Mirei show you how it's done.
I'd like to see that.
I mean, no one's ever done it before.
Yeah, yeah, yeah.
You've seen it, right?
Yes, I did.
What? I wonder.
I'll get right to it.
Hoshida-san's mute.
Here you go.
Today's show was great, about 2,000 people came to see our show.
Thank you very much.
Mirei, what's that? Your voice.
Can you hear me? Is it muted? Is it? It's not muted?
I don't know, but what is that? Are you introducing him?
Hmm? I can't tell what's going on. There's too much white.
There's too much white.
Too much white.
Oh, is he introducing cosmetics?
Are you introducing cosmetics?
This powder is really good.
Oh, that's right, that's right.
Oh, give me some foundation.
Here.
You've been doing this for a long time? That's amazing.
That's great. You don't even notice the mute.
That's great. You don't notice the mute at all.
Is this Mire-chan's favorite cosmetics?
Oh, yeah.
Ah! I haven't used this color in a while because it's so cute!
Oh, it's connected, it's connected! Mire-chan, Mire-chan!
I've had this muted for a long time.
I've been trying so hard to get this to work.
I'm introducing cosmetics now, and recently
I'm already addicted to it.
What?
It's over!
Coconner's gone. What happened?
Yes, uh, Mr. Coconner, the video has been shut down.
Can you stop filming my mute game while I'm playing my mute game?
I did! I'm sorry!
I played the real mute game! I'm sorry!
Real! I was already thinking that Cocona was the winner after the first one.
It's too real now.
Sorry!
Let's see it again!
So, the first one, Mirei, you're good!
Was she good? You were so good!
It was really muted!
Amazing!
I think I muted her while she was doing this makeup delivery by herself.
Did I really? It looked like that?
I did it!
You're so good!
This is raising the bar a little bit!
Who's next?
Kokonai?
I'm next!
Shall we go?
I've really been through the mute!
Yeah!
I've just had a real mute experience!
Yes! So here's the mute!
Here we go!
Hello, everybody!
Hello!
I just muted you!
Did I keep saying hello?
Hello!
Is this a hello stream today? I didn't hear him.
He's saying hello all the time.
Hello.
Is this thing muted? Does he know? I don't know if you've noticed.
But, I mean, I don't know, I haven't noticed. He gets really excited when I say hello.
He's going away.
What?
He's using his whole body.
You didn't say hello.
I'm sure she's just here to say hello.
Okay, well, maybe I should just mute him.
Hello.
There we are... here we are.
Did you notice? Did you just mute me?
I've been on mute.It was on mute the whole time.
I was just practicing Shikigoi-san's hello to me.
Oh, I see.
Let's go practice.
It'd be funny if it were here. I didn't know there was such a thing.
I see. You didn't know this?
What's everyone's reaction?
Hello, Loop? What kind of funny? Practice?
I'm 16 years old.
Some people recognized it the first time.
Really?
Where do you get tired?
Let's see what you've been practicing.
Hello.
I wonder if this is similar.
I wonder if it's possible without the guy who's going in there.
It's nighttime.
It was a little bit awkward. I'm a bit of a comedian.
Comic ability.
Yeah, I know.
It was my mistake. Let's reflect on that.
Let's be sorry. Yeah, let's be sorry.
Because you just gave me a perfect mute mitch.
Yeah, you're right.
Let's go, Aya.
Aya, you're right.
Okay, bye for now.
Okay, third one.
Wait a minute, I was looking at everyone else's plans and didn't make my own.
I'll just go with the flow.
Okay, here's my mute.
Ayaka Yasumoto's mute.
Here we go. Come on in.
Okay, hello everyone.
So, today's show is the first time
This is my first time.
Wait a minute, please.
Mm-hmm.
Someone's talking.
Hmm?
What? What?
What?
It's the feed, right now.
What are you doing?
What are you doing? Uh, the center.
Aya.
What are you doing? Folding?
Doraemon? Oh, you put coins in there.
Oh, well, I'm just opening it.
Do you see the similarity between my circle and Doraemon's circle?
Look, they have the same round face!
That's terrible!
No, it's not.
They look alike, don't they? What?
I'm a curvy guy. I don't look like you.
It's rude to say we look alike.
It's really rude. Hey, hey, hey.
I'm streaming right now, so keep it quiet.
I'm sorry, I'm just...
I've been watching you. And you were talking to someone.
Your mom asked me to get her clothes.
And then...
And then she said he looked like Doraemon, and started messing with him.
Yeah.
I wonder if she wanted to get out.
That kind of thing happens, doesn't it? Parents are like that.
She's been out a lot, hasn't she?
Yes.
Yes, that's why.
Was I up-decorating? It's different. It's a different game now.
I understand. I was playing up-deco.
It's a bit of a mute game.
The possibilities are endless. Anything was possible.
We could do all kinds of things. So, now that everyone is done, I'd like to decide the Queen of Mute by a little vote.
The Queen of Mute. Well, you know, each of us plays a different genre of music.
They are totally different.
I think it's difficult for everyone to judge.
So, let's see who you think is the best. Is this a survey?
Are you muted? Hoshina-san, your voice is muted.
Hoshina?
Oh, I heard it!
I had it muted for about a minute, but no one noticed.
Oh no! Hoshina-san is coming to win!
And here comes the fans' votes to add up!
The voting function is in trouble!
So, shall we vote for the most beloved Hoshina and Coconan as number 3?
Yes!
Who was the best mute queen? Please send us your criteria of who you think was the best mute.
Please send it to me!
Please do!
Oh, I wonder if there is a survey function.
Oh, there it is!
No.1 OHOSHINA No.2 YASUMOTO No.3 MOYASUMOTO
Sakuragi? I didn't put Sakuragi...
Oh, no...
Wait a minute...
I tried my best to say hello
Oh, well then...
I'll vote for Hoshina No.1, Yasumoto No.2, and Sakuragi No.3.
Please vote for me!Please vote.
Please vote for me.
Please, please, please.
Everyone seems to be making a mistake.
Wrong?
Wrong, wrong, wrong.
How's it going, how's everyone reacting?
I'm curious.
A lot of people got it wrong.
I think I made a mistake.
I didn't think you'd throw in Nishiki Koi's stuff here.
Hey...
What, you like comedy here too?
Surprisingly.
Oh, I like comedians and often watch variety TV shows
Variety TV shows
Variety TV shows.
Who's that comedian you've been into lately, Nishikikoi?
Oh, yes, I like Nishikikoi-san.
Um, I knew it, hello! Yagawa-san is so funny and cute.
So you like her.
He's so cute, Nishikikoi-san.
Nishikikoi is very popular now, isn't she?
Hey...yes.
Yes, she is, even in M1.
What do you think, the survey?
Well, shall we end it now?
Questionnaire!
Yes!
End!
So, let's see the results.
Ah! Hmm?
Number 1, Hoshina, 39.3%.
Sakuragi at number 3, 34%.
Number 2, Yatsuba and 26.7%.
Miyutoge won!
The winner! It's Miyu!
I wonder if that last attempt to score a bit of points was effective?
That was it, for sure. You did it.
That's right, you did it.
But it was closer than I thought. There wasn't that much difference.
Well, that's for sure.
And Coconut and Miyu, not so close...
That's right!
Don't worry, the voting is already over!
I have to go earn my hand now.
Here we go again.
You're good at muting.
I'm so good at muting, it might be important.
I'm good at zanabiyan this and that
The only thing I can use is this little room.
It's just a nuisance.
Mute
Yes, so
Mire-chan is in first place.
So, we'll see you next time in the form of distribution. When the boy does it too, I'd like you to show us your favorite mute trick.
I hope you'll show us your favorite mute trick when you do it again.
That's all for now.
Okay, so let's move on to the next corner, shall we?
We have two corners today.
I'll start with the first one. The title is "Delightful and Fufufufufuna
Home Music!
Yay!
This is a fun project for the remote.
We're going to play a song by Ebichu, and we're all going to get into the groove during the song.
Today's song...
Last time it was "Happy End" and "And Then"?
Yes, Happy End.
Yes, it was Megacis.
So, I want everyone to listen to the album a lot more.
So, let's play "anytime anywhere" today.
Nice shot!
Yes, sir.
What shall we do?
Who's going to play the song?
Right here.
Right here? Shall we swing?
Yes, sir.
After that, please choreograph a song that everyone can dance to.
Okay.
Let's do Shiri to Ebi Degaku by Shiri to Ebi Degaku.
Shiri to Ebi Degaku
anytime anywhere
Hi-chan, you're right about YouTube.
Does this include your voice?
Yes, it will.
It will?
I just muted it.
I just muted it on my own.
I wonder if there are fans who copied all this.
I wonder if there are.
The choreography is easy to remember.
It matches the lyrics, doesn't it?
Yes, it does.
Hey...
I like it.
It's good.
I remember eating...
This is a remote experience, but when a song comes on and you do hand gestures, you can only do it with your hands, so you don't know what you're doing.This is a remote experience, but when a song is played and you do hand gestures, you can only do it with your hands, so you don't know what to do, right?
That's true!
It was half, one shot.
I remember it in conjunction with my feet, so if I can't move my feet, I don't know what it was.
That's true, the swinging of the feet.
TikTok is amazing, because it's only with your hands.
No, I know.
So, I don't know guys.
That might be. Yes, it's hard for the older members to remember the Tik Tok choreography.
It always takes me a long time.
You are so fast at shaking your hands, aren't you?
Yes, Yuko is quick to learn hand gestures. You must be used to it.
I wish I could do it.
Yuko.
Are you getting faster?
Everyone learns really fast.
You really do.
They're doing it all the time.
They're getting faster and faster.
Maybe it's because we're prepping.
Do you remember the surprises when you're prepping?
That's all.
Let's see...the songs of EBICHU take 30 minutes at the most.
And when I see the detailed choreography, an hour goes by pretty quickly, and I remember a lot of the detailed choreography.
Yeah, but isn't it amazing to be able to memorize something like that?
Besides, you know, the vlogs are so small, people have a hard time seeing them.
It's hard to see with other people.
I guess I'm good at it because I used to watch videos of my favorite dances, copy the choreography, and upload the videos.
You must be good at it. You must be good at it.
Yes, I've done a lot of work.
I have a little problem. I learn quickly, but after a while, when I play a song I haven't played in a while,
I tend to suddenly lose track of what I'm doing.
I can understand that.
And since you play a song for a short period of time, you tend to lose track of it,
I don't know, my memory fades a little.
Yes, that's right.
That's right.
I didn't study either.
That's for sure.
Oh, sure.
I'll have to repeat that.
I mean, I talked like a normal person at a home music project.
I talked.
It was like an amazing remote development.
Because it's already over.
It's the last time, so everyone is perfect.
So, you know...
I know I talked a lot, but that's all for now.
I feel a little sick, don't I?
I feel a little sick.
I felt like talking a little bit, didn't I?
Yes, that's right.
So, there's a lot to talk about today. Let's have another corner, shall we?
Let's do it!
Next, we'll do this corner.
A fun and fufufu super screentime!
The "Lodgings Time Game"!
It's everyone's favorite "Shukusho Time"!
The rules of the game are as follows: Even though the members of Ebichu are far away from each other, I am sure they are connected.
Now, we're going to take into account the opinions of our users and try to make a variety of poses.
We're going to make various poses with the help of the three of us.
Yes!
I'm going to add a little something that the three of us can do together this time.
Shall we?
I wonder if it will be something.
Wait a minute... "love girls"?
Yes.
It's a little difficult with three people, isn't it?
I can't either.
You're right.
With two or five people, you can do a lot of things, but...
I told you that before, didn't I?
What were we talking about before?
Coconuts and... and making hearts with things.
Oh, yeah, hearts.
Hmmm...
Triangles are so easy.
Triangles?
What kind of triangles?
Like this, with your hand like this.
Like this, maybe, you know, with the three of us at the bottom of the screen.
Like this, like this, like this.
I'll do it like this.
Okay. - Okay.
Surprisingly difficult triangle.
Wait, wait, wait.
Like this.
I like this.
Yes.
Triangle.
high
like this
ah, triangles
Triangles are hard
It's important to write this down.
Is it a triangle?
It's a rug. You don't know.
You're right.
I don't know.I don't know.
I'm the other way around? Like this?
Am I doing it right?
Let me know in the comments.
What do you think?
Like, "Hey, hey, hey, hey, hey, hey, hey, hey, hey, hey, hey, hey, hey, hey, hey.
And then here, it's like, you know, open your hand a little bit more, right?
Open, yes.
Like this, like this.
Oh, I got it this way. Oh, isn't that bad?
I think you got it.
I don't know.
Did it work?
What the hell is this?
Is it working? Is it?
Can we go for a little face time? Let's get a picture of you.
Ero is so cool.
You're so cool.
The problem with this one is it darkens your face.
Maybe it is.
Did I get it, guys?
I got it.
How's it coming?
It's good.
That's good.
Okay, let's do one more normal pose, shall we?
Sure, let's do another one.
I don't know, maybe this one? The three of us don't have to stick together.
Just a cute one.
Something cute that we can all remember.
What do you think?
Ayacchan's hair color is cute.
Oh, thank you. New color.
But this one, gal... is a little off.
It's gone. It's great.
It's not too girly?
It's very gal-like.
Gal.
And here it is, the 44th edition of the Deaf Showroom, and it's coming to an end very quickly!
How was it?
I guess it's like a remote...
I always get nervous.
You're alone, you're alone, you're alone, you're alone, you're alone, you're alone, you're alone.
But there were a lot of interesting things that could only be done remotely.
It was fun.
Seven hours.
I'm always relaxed enough, but even more so than usual.
We had a relaxing and at-home atmosphere.
We are going to hold a spring tour.
We will start from Niigata this Saturday.
Is there still time to get tickets?
Yes, there are.
Yes, there are other places.
If there is a date near you that you can go, please come and see us.
I would be very happy if you could come and see the live performance of EBITCHU.
I'd be very happy if you could come and see us!
Yes, and the album too!
The album is actually on sale now.
There are many great songs on it, so I hope you will listen to it!
Lastly, let's introduce the final ranking.
Okay, let's go!
Thank you very much for coming in fifth place!
Thank you very much.
Thank you very much. And in fourth place, thank you very much to KERRY-G!
In third place, thank you ZEROONE7!
Thank you very much!
Thank you very much.
Thank you istourkee 0pen for 3rd place
Thank you very much!
Thank you 2100 people saw it
I'm so happy!
I'll see what you have to say.
Let's see what you have to say.
Yes, I see.
There are people who said they're going to Osaka.
Some are coming from other people.
And there are people from Ibaraki, too.
I'm so happy!
I'm sorry, I was right.
It was Friday.
I'm sorry, it was Friday.
No, no, no, you started on a holiday on Friday.
Oh, so Friday's a holiday.
Golden Ickfirth.
I just realized it's already Golden Week.
It's early.
It's gone by so fast!
It's May already!
May is coming!
Thank you very much for those who said May is coming!
Thank you very much.
May is coming, which means it's your major label's debut date?
May 5th is coming soon.
You know, the first anniversary...
Yeah.
I'm curious.
It's been a year that didn't fly by.It's been a year, and it didn't fly by.
It's really been a fast year. It's the first time I've had the opportunity to work with you in various capacities.
The three of us have changed a lot since May 5th last year, haven't we?
You heard that, right?
Yes, yes, yes...
I guess it's more correct to say that they look more solid.
Their eyes... yes, yes, yes... they were so different from each other.
Let's do it! I don't know, it's amazing.
It's like a sparkle. It's amazing.
It's like an idol aura was in full swing.
Yeah.
Oh, yes, Panikertosi was really squishy.
Yeah, it made you happy, didn't it?
Yeah, it made me happy.
Everyone said they could tell.
No, and, uh...
I'm glad that I got to know my sisters a little bit better.
Yeah, I guess so.
Do you still get nervous?
Not anymore.
No?
You don't get nervous anymore?
No, not anymore.
Oh, I see it again.
What?
Where did it go?
I'm trying to make this Sakurage's last hurrah.
I'm trying to connect now.
Oh, here it is! He's back!
I'm so sorry.
I'm totally sorry.
It's kind of a mute theme today.
Today...
Here's another mute queen.
It's called KL Games.
KL Games
It's fun, isn't it?
Yeah. What are the comments like?
The comments are... people are surprised at the mute.
They're covering for me, saying it's a remote thing.
Yeah, I know.
They're all saying how you just touched me in the face.
Thank you very much.
We're going to keep growing, so please come and visit us.
And thank you very much for the more than 3,000 visitors.
Thank you very much.
There were so many people, 3,000 people.
Thank you for watching.
Thank you very much.
I guess it's time to say goodbye.
Yes, it is.
So, the next broadcast is still undecided, so we'll let you know as soon as it's decided.
So please look forward to it.
And that brings us to the end of our 44th episode today.
Thank you very much.
Thank you very much for your time today.
Bye-bye, bye-bye, bye-bye.
by H. by H.
by H.